hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
Ah, which way is it?!
There's a faint scent of salt water...
We were almost there...
Then I'll use my Rasengan to...
Wait! If it doesn't go well,
we'll be crushed under the ceiling.
If so, what should we do?!
Everyone, step backward.
What?!
Phew, we're safe...!
Anko Sensei!
Let's get moving...
It's already morning.
Oh, no!
The ships collecting funds
are in danger...!
We've got to follow them
right away!
With that ship!
Okay, let's go!
You've had no contact
from the Ninja of the Leaf Village?
They were told to
accompany the ship.
What in the world happened?
Captain, we just received
communication.
I see!
That's what I expect
from elite Ninja!
It seems they finished the suppression
of the Demon of the Ocean last night.
Excellent...
So now the ships are safe.
Of course.
Men, take your positions!
We'll depart.
Despair:
A Fractured Heart
Be careful of the reef!
I don't see any ships that look like
those that collect funds in the port.
How could they depart without us?
Have they already fallen
into Amachi's scheme...?
Captain Hitode...
What happened?!
There's something there!
The bottom of the ship...!
Confirm the enemy!
Roger!
Huh? What?
Full toward port!
I can't steer!
What?
It's no good. It won't move.
We're going to hit, everyone.
Grab onto something!
This must be the attack from
the Demon of the Ocean?
Thank you for working hard
at transporting the funds.
I saw you a while ago!
Identify yourself!
If you hand this ship over
without resistance,
I will save your life.
Don't mess with me!
— It's the Demon of the Ocean...
— A monster!
Demon Illusion: Fire Jutsu.
What...?
That's...
It's fire torture...!
Yoroi, take care of the rest.
What?!
I'm your opponent!
Everyone, hang in there!
Don't be so nasty!
We meet again, weirdo!
Excuse me, but I still have
something to ask you.
What are you doing, Isaribi!
Cut it out already!
Keep this up and you'll really turn
into the Demon of the Ocean!
Do it, Isaribi.
Your opponent is right here.
You said that Orochimaru left
that research facility
a month and a half ago...
Where did he go?
I don't know...
Now that you mention it,
Orochimaru had a kid in tow.
I heard that the kid is
really excellent, unlike you.
Uchiha Sasuke.
Something about you
just wasn't enough.
That's why you were abandoned,
I guess.
Isarirbi?!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Isaribi...
I bet you still understand
what I've been saying to you, Isaribi!
Don't you care a bit after
tormenting everyone this much?
No.
I think nothing of...
even bringing you down...
That's a lie!
It doesn't matter to me
who gets injured...
or who drowns...
I'm satisfied as long as
I can return to being a human!
It's about time to come
to yourself!
I understand painfully
enough how you feel...
But... doing that...
It's not good!
Isaribi, you saved me.
You have a kind heart!
Pretty good for a Medical Ninja.
Shut up!
I'm a little surprised that
you had enough time
to take your eyes off...
Damn it!
You're too confident...
You're useless.
How long you think
you'll be doing this?
Amachi...
He's just a kid.
Why can't you finish him off
right away?
Sorry. But...
I can't take it anymore.
Get out of my way!
Bring it on.
I'll kill a damn monster like you!
Monster? Me?
That's right!
You so easily injure
and kill people.
You're a monster wearing
human skin!
Hey! What's so funny!
If so, what then?
I'm not some half-monster
like Isaribi...
I'm...
further refined than her and
fully integrated for combat use!
You...!
Amachi...!
Get out of my way!
You're an almost dead guinea pig...
What are you doing?!
Even though we were supposed to dissect
and use her as material for experiments,
we took pity on her
and kept her alive.
But after all,
she's terribly ungrateful and useless.
What's wrong... kid?
You! You're not only
a monster in body and soul!
In truth, you're scum!
C'mere... I'll play with you.
Bastard!
Idiot!
Hah, amateurish...
Not over yet!
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
No matter how many times
you come at me, you'll get the same thing!
Well, what's wrong, little guy?
You're going to come again, huh?
Yeah, of course!
Until you change Isaribi back...
I'll come at you again and again.
Water Style:
Great Cannonball Jutsu!
What's wrong,
you're done already?
Give it up already, kid!
I told you!
Until I take Isaribi back...
I absolutely will not... quit!
Why...
would you go that far
to save me?
I can't keep up with the farce.
Come on! Sea Monster!
Do it... Sea Monster!
Hey! Let go of me, you!
Let me tell you that almost all of
Sea Monster's body is made of water.
You can say it's like
a moving Water Prison Jutsu.
Naruto!
Damn...
You're stupid.
Do you think something like that
will affect it at all?
Do you understand, Isaribi?
I am the only one
who can save you.
Now, finish them off!
What's wrong?
You want to turn back into
a human, don't you?
Then do as I say!
It's no good...
I can't let Isaribi...
go to... that world...
This feeling...
"SEAL"
What?! What are these
extraordinary Chakras?
Sea Monster!
Isaribi...
I will never let Isaribi
go over there!
What are you...?!
Naruto...?!
He's the same as you.
Same as me...?!
Yes...
The Nine-Tailed Fox Spirit,
who long ago attacked our village,
is sealed inside Naruto.
And there was a time
when everyone in the village
treated him like a monster.
And...
And even so, he works so hard,
everybody approves of him.
I understand painfully enough
how you feel...
But... doing that...
It's not good.
Those words... were true...
Naruto!
You bastard!
kaze ga fuite aa
the wind blows
itai kienai omoi
the pain, the memories won't disappear
nani wo motte ikou ka
what should be brought along?
atsumete hitotsu
assemble them into a piece
nido to nai nido to nai
there is no second chance, never
suteru nante baka mitai
how foolish it is to throw away
mujaki ni natte aa
acting so innocently
imeeji
the images
kitto sore wa owaranai
it probably will not end
ai no mune kogase
burn that love-filled heart
sen no yume watare
sail across a thousand dreams
juuoumujin kakete
running freely
te ni tsukamu sekai
to take hold of the world in hand
kumo ga chigirete
the clouds scatter
hi ga mata ochite
the sun sets yet again
hitori no pareedo ga ugokidasu
the solo parade begins to move
bouken kichijitsu shinpaku joushou
adventure, lucky day, geart beat, rising
meian souguu seimei souai
decisive, encounter, life, mutual love
Oh, I was able to do
the Chief Toad summoning
for the first time in a while!
Now, prepare yourself,
you flabby Jerk!
Tomorrow will never come
for you again!
This itches!
What? It's not a good time
to be getting soared now!
It really itches.
Now, Chief Toad,
take him out good.
Naruto, summoning me in
salt water like this!
I could take your life for this!
What...?!
Next time:
"Sea Battle. The Released Power."